If I could have your attention, please.
请注意一下。
I’d like to talk to you about young people’s screen time.
我想和大家谈谈年轻人的屏幕使用时间。
It’s a tempting habit for them to glance at their smartphone or tablet rather than make eye contact with someone and make conversation!
对他们来说，瞥一眼智能手机或平板电脑，而非与人进行眼神交流、展开对话，已经成了一种难以抗拒的习惯！
There is so much to look at: photographs, social media feeds, messages and emails; it’s no wonder they are glued to their screens.
屏幕上有太多可看的内容：照片、社交媒体动态、信息和邮件，难怪他们会紧盯着屏幕不放。
But is it good for them?
但这对他们真的好吗？
There have been many claims about the damage looking at screens does to our eyesight.
关于看屏幕对视力造成的伤害，一直有很多说法。
Some people feared staring at a small bright box could make us short-sighted or lead to headaches.
有人担心，盯着一个明亮的小屏幕方块会导致近视或头痛。
This is a particular concern for children and young people, who spend a higher percentage of time using electronic gadgets.
这一点对儿童和年轻人来说尤为令人担忧，因为他们使用电子设备的时间占比更高。
BBC technology correspondent, Rory Cellan-Jones, says: “there is plenty of anecdotal evidence that no matter how long teenagers are spending looking at screens, they are encountering material about issues such as anorexia and self-harm that could prove damaging to their mental health”.
英国广播公司科技记者罗里·塞兰-琼斯表示：“有大量轶事证据表明，无论青少年花多长时间看屏幕，他们都会接触到有关厌食症、自残等问题的内容，这些内容可能会对他们的心理健康造成损害。”
But a new study says time in front of computers and phones might not be as bad for young people as many think.
但一项新的研究表明，在电脑和手机前花费的时间，对年轻人来说可能并不像许多人想象的那么糟糕。
Research by the Oxford Internet Institute examined data from more than 17,000 teenagers in the UK, Ireland and the United States.
牛津互联网研究所的研究分析了来自英国、爱尔兰和美国的17000多名青少年的数据。
Their study concluded that most links between life satisfaction and social media use were "trivial", accounting for less than 1% of a teenager's wellbeing.
研究得出结论，生活满意度与社交媒体使用之间的大多数关联都是“微不足道的”，仅占青少年幸福感的不到1%。
Professor Przybylski, director of research at the institute, said: "99.75% of a person's life satisfaction has nothing to do with their use of social media."
该研究所的研究主任普日比尔斯基教授表示：“一个人的生活满意度中，99.75%与社交媒体的使用无关。”
The research found that family, friends and school life all had a greater impact on wellbeing.
研究发现，家庭、朋友和学校生活对幸福感的影响都更大。
So, does this mean young people can spend longer looking at social media?
那么，这是否意味着年轻人可以花更长时间浏览社交媒体呢？
The Oxford researchers are confident that their study is robust in its findings and that any correlation between screen time and mental health is very small.
牛津大学的研究人员对他们的研究结果充满信心，认为屏幕使用时间与心理健康之间的任何关联都非常微弱。
Dr Max Davie, officer for health improvement at the Royal College of Paediatrics and Child Health, calls the study a “small first step”, but he said there were other issues to explore, such as screen time's interference with other important activities like sleep, exercise and time with family or friends.
皇家儿科与儿童健康学院健康改善官员马克斯·戴维博士称这项研究是“小小的第一步”，但他表示还有其他问题需要探索，比如屏幕使用时间对睡眠、运动、陪伴家人或朋友等其他重要活动的干扰。
Perhaps for now, deciding what the ‘right’ amount of screen time is has to be down to personal judgement.
或许目前来看，确定屏幕使用时间的“合理”时长，还得靠个人判断。